{"surveys":[{"id":1,"name":"NPS","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answers":["1 Not at all likely","2","3","4","5","6","7","8","9","10 Highly likley"],"response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]}},{"id":2,"name":"Employee Satisfaction","content":{"questions":[{"question":"How satisfied are you at this company?","answers":["Very unsatisfied","Unsatisied","Neutral","Satisfied","Very satisfied"]}]}},{"id":3,"name":"Lunch Order","content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answers":["Pizza","Sandwiches","Sushi","Tacos"]}]}}],"responses":[{"id":77747295293,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T21:41:17.187Z"},{"id":707320912578,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},{"id":753380922800,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"What would you like for lunch today?","answer":"Pizza"}]},"completed":"2021-05-25T22:20:25.259Z"},{"id":752796782296,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":1,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T11:36:52.744Z"},{"id":691399759872,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":2,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T11:36:53.166Z"},{"id":546892283618,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"2","response":{"2":1,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T11:44:36.768Z"},{"id":629358365147,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":1,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:04:28.382Z"},{"id":50357238376,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":2,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:04:28.546Z"},{"id":147339526683,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":3,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:04:28.694Z"},{"id":733268686998,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"4","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":1,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:08:16.306Z"},{"id":272278768816,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"1 Not at all likely","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":1,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:20:34.588Z"},{"id":688832081076,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"1 Not at all likely","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":2,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T12:20:43.725Z"},{"id":840367929430,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"2","response":{"2":1,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:06:58.702Z"},{"id":939473818966,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"7","response":{"2":0,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":1,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:13:37.082Z"},{"id":796860089693,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3","response":{"2":0,"3":1,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":1,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:13:48.193Z"},{"id":98000780869,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"3","response":{"2":0,"3":2,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":1,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:13:48.339Z"},{"id":44259172743,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"6","response":{"2":0,"3":2,"4":0,"5":0,"6":1,"7":1,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:15:00.047Z"},{"id":239826388386,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"2","response":{"2":1,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:22.025Z"},{"id":319858655728,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"2","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":0}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:27.503Z"},{"id":271949906414,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":1}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:54.287Z"},{"id":454548403681,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":2}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:58.480Z"},{"id":533135858233,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":3}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:58.622Z"},{"id":207114670956,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":4}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:58.779Z"},{"id":54784262307,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":5}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:58.905Z"},{"id":694882695972,"content":{"questions":[{"question":"How likely are you to recommend our product?","answer":"10 Highly likley","response":{"2":2,"3":0,"4":0,"5":0,"6":0,"7":0,"8":0,"9":0,"1 Not at all likely":0,"10 Highly likley":6}}]},"completed":"2022-10-28T13:39:59.046Z"}]}
